[{"answer": "It is wrong to give up on children who are still missing.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "If she is, will her parents ever find her?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "Of course my reason for writing it all down is quite different to the reason to publish it as a book.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Why have you done the book?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Gerry, obviously, that is the crux of this, isn't it, for you?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "It certainly was.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "To be here, years later, and have no idea where she is or what may have happened, it must be excruciating, isn't it?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "I don't think it consumes every minute as it did before.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "I mean, Kate, do you ever have a day where this doesn't consume you?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Has that even entered your thought process?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "I don't think -- I don't think we can say 100 percent.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Or do you have to believe that?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Is that what you think?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Definitely not.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "In terms of the normal practice, though, when you were with them, would you ever have left them alone in that situation if you'd been at home, for example, back in England?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, it's not a question of money.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Another criticism as put to you is why didn't you just pay to have a nanny if you wanted to go out to dinner?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, because of what's happened, you know.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Do you feel that?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, went back to do a check at 10:00 and I went through the patio doors at the back.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "What was the exact moment -- let me ask you, Kate -- when you realized Madeleine had gone?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "I thought someone's taken her.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "And what did you think in that moment?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "You went down to tell Gerry straight away?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "The first thing that went straight through my head and I think -- it was just disbelief.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "What are you thinking?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I mean no doubt, there are a number of options.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Do you know -- is there any evidence how this person came in the room?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "There's nothing they could find to say this is unequivocally how this person came in?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Well, it's one of those things.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Did that set alarm bells off when she did that?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Now given the time that's gone past?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Have there been a number of burglaries there?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "No, we're not sure.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Do you know all the figures for that?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "I'm absolutely certain that there are things that could be done based on the information that's available to us.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Do you believe that if enough time and money and resources devoted to this, that there's some stone that's been left unturned in this investigation?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "The first police that turned up were what we call G&R police.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "What was the mood like?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Certainly.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Did you think -- did you think, Gerry, from the start that they were suspicious of you?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "You have to remember, there were nine people in the party here who didn't expect anything of this kind to happen.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Has there been anything that if an outside lawyer looked at this, they would say, that doesn't add up?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I think the key thing is -- I mean, as I say, behind the scenes --", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "How did you manage to keep your composure?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Were you offered if you'd -- if you accept that you did this, you can go to prison for two years and be out?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "It's true.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "You know, it was a great story for the media.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "That must have been a pretty awful experience, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "It's incredibly difficult, Piers, because if you speak to -- here on in the island, the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children, who've got the most expertise in these types of stranger or stereotypical kidnappings.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Are there any that you think have any kind of credibility that you think should be really pushed further?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "I think that's without doubt, really.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Do you think this could have split up many couples?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "It's been incredibly difficult.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "I mean, at its worst, what's it been like trying to have a relationship through this?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Did either of you ever get suicidal?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "I think it's the one medium that really brings her back to me, in particular, seeing her moving and her voice.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "How hard is it for you to see video footage of Madeleine, even now?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Well, at that point, it was just incredibly important.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "What was that like for you, Kate?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "He just very simply took a photograph of Madeleine and placed his palm on it and blessed her.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "What did he say to you?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "It's challenged my faith.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Has what's happened to you damaged your faith?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Gerry, do you still keep Madeleine's room as it always was?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Brilliantly.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "How have they dealt with it?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Well, they know that a man has taken her.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "What do they think happened to Madeleine?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Well, what we've done the last few -- few years, we have marked the day.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "How do you deal with a birthday when she's not there?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "I think it's two things.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "If you're watching this interview and you're keen to try and help you in some way in the search for Madeleine, what is the most effective way that people can do this?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Certainly believe it wouldn't have changed.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "And do you know if that would be still there if she's now eight years old?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "They should call the police, local police.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "If people see somebody they think could possibly be Madeleine, who should they call?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Have there been moments when you've been pretty much confident that you may have found her?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Do you still have any kind of conversation with her?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "I can, actually, yeah.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Can you sleep OK now?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "I think, overall, it gives you hope.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Do you think there's hope, or is it almost like a knife in your back that Madeleine hasn't?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "I'd say, Madeleine, we're still looking for you and if you get a chance, tell the police who you are.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "If she was, what would you say to her?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "I would just say, you know, we love you, Madeleine.", "docId": "110511pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "ORGAN: Kate, what would you -- what would you say, if you had the chance?", "qSentId": 619}]